Guide to the Fortnightly Music Club Records SC0518
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Fortnightly Music Club records
circa 1910-2008
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Fortnightly Music Club
SC0518
.25 Linear Feet
Printed ephemera, clippings, photographs and other materials, many assembled during the club's 75th anniversary in 1983; and their Centennial Memory Album issued in 2008.
Information about Access
This collection is open for research.
Biographical/Historical Sketch
Music club with members primarily from the Stanford University and Palo Alto, California, communities.
Description of the Collection
Printed ephemera, clippings, photographs and other materials, many assembled during the club's 75th anniversary in 1983; and their Centennial Memory Album issued in 2008.
Music.; Fortnightly Music Club; Fortnightly Music Club; Stanford University. Department of Music
- Records
  - News Clippings-Early members: Lydia Mitchell, M/M Charles Moser, Sara Harker Anniversary notices in paper: 40th, 50th, 60th, 75th, undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Constitution & bylaws; letter to membership about meeting venues, 1910; 1939 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Letter to secretary Mrs. George J. Peirce from Gertrude Marx, 1910 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Diamond Jubilee programs, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - “Fortnightly profiles: a vignette into the past” Elizabeth R. Cole; Talk by Cole at the 75th anniversary celebration, 1/9/1983, 1982-9-23; 1983-1-9 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Photographs, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Programs and newsletters including “Peninsula Musical Association", undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Season brochure, 1925-1926 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Programs and other ephemera, undated (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Centennial Memory Album; handouts, 1908-2008 (Box 1, Folder 10)